# Odunayo Ayodeji Fawumi

Ogbomosho, Oyo, Nigeria



fawumiodunayo@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/odunayo-ayodeji-fawumib2b47a209

## Summary

Experienced Frontend Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Firebase, Typescript, Nodejs, Vue.js, JavaScript, Redux, and React.js. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from Ladoke Akintola University of Technology.

# **Experience**



### **Frontend Developer**

Micakin

Nov 2020 - Present (9 months +)



## Frontend Developer (Intern)

Bowen University Iwo Nov 2020 - Apr 2021 (6 months)

#### **Education**



## Ladoke Akintola University of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2015 - 2021

#### Skills

Front-end Development • JavaScript • Node.js • PSD to HTML • HTML5 • React.js • React Native • Firebase • Vue.js • Vuex